Finding Aid for the Medical Artifacts Collection
Eskind Biomedical Library Manuscripts Collection
- Box 88 601 Sebrell, William H. Certificate, written in Spanish, hand lettered and drawn proclamation signed by approximately 75 people and presented to William H. Sebrell, Jr., M.D. in August, 1967, for his work. Rolled and contained in a mailing tube (paper is very yellowed and brittle). Donated by Mrs. Helena Sebrell, April 2, 1993.
- Box 88 602 Sebrell, William H. Certificate, from Lebanon and written in Arabic presented to William H. Sebrell, Jr., M.D. (rolled and good condition). Donated by Mrs. Helena Sebrell, April 2, 1993.
- Box 88 603 Sebrell, William H. Certificate presented to William H. Sebrell, Jr., M.D. stating that he visited Australia in April, 1974 (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Helena Sebrell, April 2, 1993.
- Box 88 604 Sebrell, William H. Certificate, written in Spanish from the "Orden Rodolfo Robles," and hand-lettered and written on parchment paper and presented to William H. Sebrell, Jr., M.D., on September 15, 1959 (rolled and in good condition). Donated by Mrs. Helena Sebrell, April 2, 1993.
- Box 88 605 Sebrell, William H. Certificate from the U. S. Japan Cooperative Medical Science Program awarded to Dr. W. Henry Sebrell, Jr. in appreciation for service. 1967-71 (good condition, stored flat). Donated by Mrs. Helena Sebrell, April 5, 1993.
- Box 88 606 Sebrell, William H. Certificate, hand-lettered, from the Research Corporation in recognition for distinguished service in combating malnutrition. Presented to William H. Sebrell, Jr., M.D., in Port au Prince Haiti, June 12, 1973 (good condition, contained in a blue heavy-paper folder). Donated by Mrs. Helena Sebrell, April 2, 1993.
- Box 88 607 Sebrell, William H. Certificate from the University of Virginia School of Medicine presented to William H. Sebrell, Jr., M.D. on May 8, 1981 in recognition of his support (good condition, stored flat). Donated by Mrs. Helena Sebrell, April 2, 1993.
- Box 88 607A Sebrell, William H. Certificate from Columbia University presented to William H. Sebrell, Jr., M.D. on July 1, 1970, in recognition of distinguished service as a member of the faculty of the Department of Medicine (good condition contained in a blue cover). Donated by Mrs. Helena Sebrell, April 2, 1993.
- Box 88 607B Sebrell, William H. Certificate from the American Public Health Association presented to William H. Sebrell, Jr., M.D., in 1977 in tribute to his service (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Helena Sebrell, April 2, 1993.
- Box 25 609 "Dieulafoy's Aspirator" or stomach pump, ca. 1900. Manufactured by the Godman & Shurtleef Co., Boston. Contains directions and is in a nickel plated metal case with a floral pattern stamped on its top, (fair condition). Donated by Mr. Joe Hanson, May 27, 1993.
- Box 25 610 Six surgical stainless steel instruments containing small light bulbs ca. 1910. Manufactured by the Electro-Surgical Instrument Co., Rochester, NY. Instruments contained in a leather wooden covered box, 12" x 7.5" x 5.5." (fair condition). Donated by Mr. Joe Hanson, May 27, 1993.
- Box 25 608 Three leather cases. Two of which contain phials of medicine and the other containing various small medical instruments which belonged to Dr. Archibald C. Waters. Ca. 1900, good condition. Note: That artifact numbers 608-619 belonged to Dr. A. C. Waters. Donated by Mr. Joe Hanson, May 27, 1993.
- Box 25 611 Amber colored bottle in a wire cage, ac 1900 (fair condition). Donated by Mr. Joe Hanson, May 27, 1993.
- Box 25 612 Syringes, needles, etc. ca. 1900-1920, contained in a plastic bag (fair condition). Donated by Mr. Joe Hanson, May 27, 1993.
- Box 25 613 Sutures, suture silk, and catgut, ca 1910. Sutures are contained in two cases; one leather and one metal. Donated by Mr. Joe Hanson, May 27, 1993.
- Box 25 614 Surgical clamps, forceps and needle holders ca. 1900-1920. Contained in a plastic bag (rusty). Donated by Mr. Joe Hanson, May 27, 1993.
- Box 25 615 Surgical probes, nine miscellaneous, ca. 1900-1920. Contained in plastic bag (fair condition). Donated by Mr. Joe Hanson, May 27, 1993.
- Box 25 616 Obstetrical instruments, miscellaneous, including a speculum and a scale, ca. 1900. Contained in a plastic bag (good condition). Donated by Mr. Joe Hanson, May 27, 1993.
- Box 25 617 Medical instruments, miscellaneous including: forceps, stethoscope, and speculum, ca 1900 (fair condition). Donated by Mr. Joe Hanson, May 27, 1993.
- Box 25 618 Phonendoscope, manufactured by the Bazzi-Bianchi Bowles Co., Rome, patented October 2, 1894. Contained in a cylindrical metal case (good condition). Donated by Mr. Joe Hanson, May 27, 1993.
- Box 25 619 Three labeled boxes containing medical products including: one colon tube manufactured by the Lee Tire & Rubber Co., and two ampoules of pituitary liquid manufactured by Armour & Co. (Also: 4 hypodermic needles, one small bottle of hypodermic tablets, and an empty box for aseptic syringes manufactured by the Doster-Northington Co.) all ca. 1920. Donated by Mr. Joe Hanson, May 27, 1993.
- Box 25 620 Syringe opener manufactured by the Becton Dickinson Company, ca. 1960.
- Box 25 621 Utility syringe outfit manufactured by the Becton Dickinson Company, ca. 1960.
- Box 26 622 Test tubes, micro pipets, and two glass markers. Contained in a box (Good condition). Note: Artifact numbers 622-650 as well as numbers 742-747 were all donated by Mrs. R. N. Holmes in June of 1993. All of the instruments and attachments belonged to her and her husband. Donated by Mrs. R. N. Holmes, June, 1993.
- Box 26 623 Rheostat transformer (used to regulate electrical currents for an arc lamp), ca. 1920, manufactured by the E. Leitz, Wetzlar, Germany (good condition). Donated by Mrs. R. N. Holmes, June 7, 1993.
- Box 26 624 Carrying case for slide specimens. Donated by Mrs. R. N. Holmes, June 7, 1993.
- Box 26 625 Case, brushed metal, containing six tweezers and forceps (good condition). Donated by Mrs. R. N. Holmes, June 7, 1993.
- Box 26 626 Scales contained in a wooden case. Also contains weights ca. 1920 (good condition). Donated by Mrs. R. N. Holmes, June 7, 1993.
- Box 26 627 Dark-field microscope condenser manufactured by E. Leitz, Wetzlar, Germany, ca. 1910. Contained in a case (good condition). Donated by Mrs. R. N. Holmes, June 7, 1993.
- Box 26 628 Ocular screw-micrometer eye-piece manufactured by the Carl Zeiss Co., Germany. Contained in a black-leather-covered case (good condition). Donated by Mrs. R. N. Holmes, June 7, 1993.
- Box 26 629 Dark-field illuminator, ca. 1910 manufactured by the Spencer Company. In a brown carrying case (good condition). Donated by Mrs. R. N. Holmes, June 7, 1993.
- Box 26 630 Micro-polariscopes, two, containing two nickel prisms used for polarizing objects, ca. 1920. Manufactured by the Spencer Co. Contained in a wooden box (good condition). Donated by Mrs. R. N. Holmes, June 7, 1993.
- Box 26 631 Two glass bull's eye lenses, and two other lenses. (good condition). Donated by Mrs. R. N. Holmes, June 7, 1993.
- Box 26 632 Microscope attachments. Box containing an ocular lens, an above the stage condenser, and other miscellaneous microscope attachments. Donated by Mrs. R. N. Holmes, June 7, 1993.
- Box 26 633 Condenser with an iris diaphragm ca. 1920. Manufactured by the Spencer Co. In a black case (good condition). Donated by Mrs. R. N. Holmes, June 7, 1993.
- Box 26 634 Spectroscope, ca. 1920. Manufactured by Ernest Leitz, Wetzlar, Germany. Contained in a brown case (good condition). Donated by Mrs. R. N. Holmes, June 7, 1993.
- Box 26 635 Syringe for anti-diphtheria injections, ca. 1910. Contained in a wooden box with directions written in French (good condition). Donated by Mrs. R. N. Holmes, June 7, 1993.
- Box 26 636 Pipets and tubes. Contained in a wooden "Ten-Ten" cigar box. Donated by Mrs. R. N. Holmes, June 7, 1993.
- Box 26 637 Eye-piece attachment used to assist in the drawing of specimens ca. 1925. Manufactured by Ernest Leitz, Wetzlar, Germany. Contained in a case (good condition). Donated by Mrs. R. N. Holmes, June 7, 1993.
- Box 26 638 Microscope attachment, unidentified. Manufactured by Bausch and Lomb Optical Company, Rochester, New York. Donated by Mrs. R. N. Holmes, June 7, 1993.
- Box 26 639 Microscope lamp ca. 1920 Manufactured by Leitz. Contained in a box which also contains bulbs (good condition). Donated by Mrs. R. N. Holmes, June 7, 1993.
- Box 26 640 Box containing slides of mosquitoes. Donated by Mrs. R. N. Holmes, June 7, 1993.
- Box 26 641 Miscellaneous microscope instruments and parts including: "warm stage material," attachment block for single-cell manipulator, and micro-condenser attachments. Donated by Mrs. R. N. Holmes, June 7, 1993.
- Box 26 642 Miscellaneous microscope equipment including: slides, single cell manipulator slides, and other micro-manipulator material. Contained in a "King Edward" cigar box. Donated by Mrs. R. N. Holmes, June 7, 1993.
- Box 26 643 Dividers and small screw drivers contained in a red box. Donated by Mrs. R. N. Holmes, June 7, 1993.
- Box 26 644 Surgical scissors and tweezers contained in a box. Donated by Mrs. R. N. Holmes, June 7, 1993.
- Box 26 645 Tubing clams and rubber stoppers contained in a red box Donated by Mrs. R. N. Holmes, June 7, 1993.
- Box 26 646 Test tubes, nine, contained in a blue box. Donated by Mrs. R. N. Holmes, June 7, 1993.
- Box 26 647 Mechanical stage attachment (to facilitate precise movement of slides) ca. 1925. Manufactured by the Spencer Co., Buffalo, NY. Contained in brown leather covered case (good condition). Donated by Mrs. R. N. Holmes, June 7, 1993.
- Box 26 648 Microscope, small hand-held. Brass tube _" in length and _" in diameter containing two lenses. Attached metal handle is 1_" in length. Ca. 18th to early 19th century (See Hogg, Jabez. The Microscope. page 6). Donated by Mrs. R. N. Holmes, June 7, 1993.
- Box 26 649 Spectroscope. Brass tube 2" in length and 1" in diameter. Contains removable lens at one end, and a prism at the other. Stamped "Made in France" on the prism end. Ca. 1870 (See Hogg, Jabez. The Microscope p. 114). Donated by Mrs. R. N. Holmes, June 7, 1993.
- Box 26 650 Unidentified microscope attachment. Brass 2.5" x .5," three parts, attached with hinges. One part contains a lens and another has a square cut-out. Donated by Mrs. R. N. Holmes, June 7, 1993.
- Box 70 651 Certificate, framed, from Alpha Omega Alpha Honor Fraternity recognizing Rudolph H. Kampmeier as being elected to its membership on April 25, 1922 (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, June 15, 1993.
- Box 70 652 Certificate, framed, from the American College of Physicians recognizing the election of Rudolph H. Kampmeier, M.D. into its membership on April 12, 1929 (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, June 15, 1993.
- Box 70 653 License, framed, from the State Board of Medical Examiners of Tennessee. Issued to Rudolph H. Kampmeier, M.D. on April 21, 1937 (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, June 15, 1993.
- Box 70 654 Certificate, framed, from the American Board of Internal Medicine certifying that Rudolph H. Kampmeier, M.D. is fit to practice internal medicine. Dated July 1, 1937 (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, June 15, 1993.
- Box 70 655 Certificate, framed, from the Office of Scientific Research and Development recognizing the work of Rudolph H. Kampmeier, M.D. Dated March 1, 1945 (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, June 15, 1993.
- Box 70 656 Certificate, framed, recognizing Rudolph H. Kampmeier, M.D. as a charter member of the "Shaef Nud-trition Mission," Dated July, 1945. (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, June 15, 1993.
- Box 70 657 Certificate, framed, from the War Department expressing appreciation for Rudolph H. Kampmeier's participation in ration field trials, and nutrition surveys (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, June 15, 1993.
- Box 70 658 Certificate, framed, proclaiming Rudolph H. Kampmeier, M.D. as Outstanding Physician of Tennessee. Awarded by the Tennessee Medical Association in 1958 (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, June 15, 1993.
- Box 70 659 Certificate, framed, declaring Rudolph H. Kampmeier, M.D. as a life member of the American College of Physicians. Dated Feb 1, 1961 (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, June 15, 1993.
- Box 70 660 Plaque from the Southern Medical Association declaring Rudolph H. Kampmeier, M.D. as a life member, June 17, 1961 (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, June 15, 1993.
- Box 70 661 Plaque from the World Forum on Syphilis and other Treponematoses presented to Rudolph H. Kampmeier, M.D. for his contribution, on September 8, 1962 (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, June 15, 1993.
- Box 70 663 Certificate of appreciation, framed, from the Southern Medical Association presented to Rudolph H. Kampmeier, M.D. on November 3, 1965 for services rendered (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, June 15, 1993.
- Box 70 664 Certificate of appreciation framed, from the Depatement of Health Education and Welfare presented to Rudolph H. Kampmeier, M.D. in [1967?] (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, June 15, 1993.
- Shelf 11 665 Kampmeier, Rudolph H. Certificate, framed, from the Royal College of Physicians of London conferring upon Rudolph H. Kampmeier, M.D. all the privleges of being a fellow in the College. Written in Latin and dated October, 1968 (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, June 15, 1993.
- Shelf 11 666 Kampmeier, Rudolph H. Certificate, framed, from the Royal College of Physicians of Ireland bestowing upon Rudolph H. Kampmeier, M.D. an honorary membership in the College. Written in Latin, dated October, 1968 (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, June 15, 1993.
- Shelf 11 667 Kampmeier, Rudolph H. Plaque from the American Medical Association presented to Rudolph H. Kampmeier, M.D. in appreciation of his contribution as a member of the Residency Review Committee, 1969 (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, June 15, 1993.
- Box 70 668 Certificate, framed, from the American College of Physicians presented to Rudolph H. Kampmeier, M.D. enumerating offices held [1971?] (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, June 15, 1993.
- Shelf 11 669 Kampmeier, Rudolph H. Certificate, framed, from the American College of Physicians conferring upon Rudolph H. Kampmeier, M.D. Master of the American College of Physicians on April 17, 1972 (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, June 15, 1993.
- Box 71 670 Certificate, framed Alfred Stengel Memorial Award from the American College of Physicians presented to Rudolph H. Kampmeier, M.D. on April 9, 1973 (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, June 15, 1993.
- Box 71 672 Plaque, Thomas H. Parran Award from the American Venereal Disease Association presented to Rudolph H. Kampmeier, M.D. in [1975?] (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, June 15, 1993.
- Box 71 673 Plaque, William Freeman Snow Award from the American Social Health Association presented to Rudolph H. Kampmeier, M.D. in 1979 (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, June 15, 1993.
- Box 71 674 Plaque, from Vanderbilt presented to Rudolph H. Kampmeier, M.D. in recognition of services as Chairman of the Living Endowment Fund, 1978-79 (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, June 15, 1993.
- Box 71 675 Plaque from the Tennessee Academy of Family Physicians presented to Rudolph H. Kampmeier, M.D. in recognition of his contribution to medicine, 1980 (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, June 15, 1993.
- Box 71 676 Certificate, framed Ralph O. Claypoole, Sr. Memorial Award from the American College of Physicians awarded to Rudolph H. Kampmeier, M.D. on April 6, 1981 (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, June 15, 1993.
- Box 71 677 Plaque, commendation from the Tennessee Medical Association presented to Rudolph H. Kampmeier, M.D. on April 11, 1981 in recognition of his writing the history of the association (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, June 15, 1993.
- Box 71 678 Plaque, President's Award, from the Nashville Academy of Medicine and Davidson County Medical Association presented to Rudolph H. Kampmeier, M.D. on January 8, 1983 (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, June 15, 1993.
- Box 71 679 Illustration, framed, of an explanation of the arms of the Royal College of Physicians of London (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, June 15, 1993.
- Box 71 680 Photograph, framed, of a Gothic facade general hospital building [perhaps the University of Iowa College of Medicine] (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, June 15, 1993.
- Box 71 681 Photograph, color, framed, of members of various English speaking colleges of physicians --including Rudolph H. Kampmeier, M.D. (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, June 15, 1993.
- Box 71 682 Photograph, framed, of Rudolph H. Kampmeier, M.D., et. al. Description at bottom of photograph (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, June 15, 1993.
- Box 71 683 Photograph, framed, group photograph taken at the Tercentenary Celebration of the Royal College of Physicians, Dublin, Ireland, May, 1967. Includes Rudolph H. Kampmeier, M.D., description at bottom (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, June 15, 1993.
- Box 73-D 684 Print, reproduction of a painting of the University of Iowa Medical School distributed by E. R. Squibb and Sons Co. (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, July 9, 1993.
- Box 73-D 685 Certificate of appointment to the Senior Citizens Committee from the Metropolitan Government, Nashville and Davidson County presented to Rudolph H. Kampmeier, M.D. on May 22, 1963 (in large white envelope, good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, July 9, 1993.
- Box 73-D 686 Poster boards with cut and paste newspaper headlines about Rudolph H. Kampmeier, M.D. (two boards contained in a large manilla envelope, good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, July 9, 1993.
- Box 73-D 687 Maps of Nome, Alaska region (two) hand drawn; and two charts pertaining to syphilis. (Contained in a large manilla envelope good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, July 9, 1993.
- Box 73-D 688 Caricatures of members of the Vanderbilt School of Medicine ca. 1950. One sheet is original, and the other is a photographic copy (contained in a large manilla envelope, good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, July 9, 1993.
- Box 73-D 689 Licenses form the states of Iowa, Utah, Indiana, Colorado, and Louisiana certifying that Rudolph H. Kampmeier, M.D. in allowed to practice medicine in these states (Rolled in a cardboard tube good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, July 9, 1993.
- Box 73-D 690 Diploma and degrees of Rudolph H. Kampmeier from Iowa City High School (1916), and State University of Iowa (A.B. 1920, M.D. 1923), Rolled in metal tube, good condition. Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, July 9, 1993.
- Box 65 691 Cap and gown worn by Rudolph H. Kampmeier, M.D. as president of the American College of Physicians. Black with gold-trimmed green stripes on the sleeves (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, July 9, 1993.
- Box 69 692 Bed pan, metal, with white enamel finish, ca. 1920, Contained in a black carrying case (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, July 9, 1993.
- Box 73-D 693 Poster board announcing the Syphilis Symposium honoring Rudolph H. Kampmeier, M.D. May 17-18, 1963. Board is red with white lettering (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, July 9, 1993.
- Box 73-D 694 Certificate of an award of Merit from the State of Tennessee presented to Rudolph H. Kampmeier, M.D. in recognition of 35 years’ service to the Middle Tennessee Mental Health Institute, May 18, 1978. Certificate in brown folder with state seal (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, July 9, 1993.
- Box 73-D 695 Six medals and desk weights presented to Rudolph H. Kampmeier, M.D. from the American College of Physicians, Canby Robinson Society, Tennessee Medical Association, and Vanderbilt University. (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, July 9, 1993.
- Box 64 696 Sphygmomanometer ca.1930 manufactured by the E. A. Baum Co. Inc., New York. Contained in a brown wooden case. The name "Dr. T. R. Harrison" is carved on the back (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, July 9, 1993.
- Box 64 697 Sphygmomanometer, ca. 1960 manufactured by the Proper Mfg. Co., Long Island, NY. Contained in a tan vinyl carrying case. Includes directions (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, July 9, 1993.
- Box 64 698 Sphygmomanometer, "Lumisphyg," ca. 1960, manufactured in Japan. In a black leather carrying case (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, July 9, 1993.
- Box 64 699 Ophthalmoscope ca. 1950, manufactured by the Bausch and Lomb Co., Rochester, NY. Contained in a black vinyl covered box, contains directions (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, July 9, 1993.
- Box 64 700 Ophthalmoscope ca. 1960, manufactured by the Bausch and Lomb Co., Rochester, NY. Contained in a black vinyl covered box (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, July 9, 1993.
- Box 64 701 Miscellaneous medical instruments ca. 1950, including: a flashlight and a tuning fork. Contained in a black leather carrying case (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, July 9, 1993.
- Box 64 702 Miscellaneous medical instruments, including glass syringes, suture needles and glass pipets. Contained in a plastic bag. Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, July 9, 1993.
- Box 64 703 Human cranium bone top with the name "Hoffman" carved on the side. Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, July 9, 1993.
- Box 64 704 Miscellaneous medical instruments, including: two reflex hammers, and a rectal speculum. Contained in a plastic bag. Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, July 9, 1993.
- Box 68 705 Apothecary bottle, large, hand blown, ca. 1900. Labeled: Anthemis. Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, July 9, 1993.
- Box 71 706 Plaque, wooden with the R. H. Kampmeier dedication issue of the Southern Medical Journal laminated on top. (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, July 9, 1993.
- Box 65 707 Plate, Wedgewood bone china, white with gold rim and two coats of arms. Commissioned in memory of Lord Resenheim, P.R.C.P. (good condition). Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, July 9, 1993.
- Box 73-D 708 Record, phonograph, of Vanderbilt Faculty Club presenting songs from the musical comedy Founder's Capers. Copyright 1961. Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, July 9, 1993.
- Box 73-D 709 Plaque, from the Alton Ochsner Medical Foundation, New Orleans. Presented to R. H. Kampmeier in recognition of being a guest speaker, September 24, 1969. Donated by Mrs. Rudolph H. Kampmeier, July 9, 1993.
- Box 60 710 Paperboard, brown, oval, framed, with gold-letter inscription:"Duncan College Preparatory School.. Class of 1948." Donated by Dr. Philip Wyatt Felts, September 20, 1993.
- Box 60 711 Diploma, framed, from Duncan College Preparatory School awarded to Philip W. Felts, June 1, 1948. Donated by Dr. Philip Wyatt Felts, September 20, 1993.
- Box 60 712 Diploma, framed, from Vanderbilt University for the Bachelor of Arts Degree awarded to Philip W. Felts, June 8, 1952. Donated by Dr. Philip Wyatt Felts, September 20, 1993.